翻译，特效，压制: 布尔
字体: 思源宋体 SemiBold
思源黑体 Medium
Yesterday, all my troubles seemed so far away
放在往日 一切烦恼仿佛那么遥远
Now it looks as though they're here to stay
如今却似乎都缠绕着我不肯离去
Oh, I believe in yesterday
我沉迷于往日
学习音轨在简介中的原简介赞助页面中
Suddenly, I'm not half to man I used to be
突然间 我已不再是曾经的自己
There's a shadow hanging over me
阴云笼罩着我的一切
Oh, yesterday came suddenly
昨天来得那么突然
Why she had to go
她为何必须得离开
I don't know she wouldn't say
因为她不说我也不知道
I said something wrong
或许是我说错过什么
Now I long for yesterday
现在的我是多么渴望往日的生活
Yesterday, love was such an easy game to play
往日 爱是如此触手可及
Now I need a place to hide away
如今我却需要隐藏自我
Oh, I believe in yesterday
哦 我沉迷于往日
Why she had to go
她为何必须得离开
I don't know she wouldn't say
因为她不说我也不知道
I said something wrong
或许是我说错过什么
Now I long for yesterday
现在的我是多么渴望往日的生活
Yesterday, love was such an easy game to play
往日 爱是如此触手可及
Now I need a place to hide away
如今我却需要隐藏自我
Oh, I believe in yesterday
哦 我沉迷于往日